That reminds me! I love how crispy they fry up all the salmon here!
Hey, for you!
It's the unlimited rice refills!
Yeah, and I can eat omelets until I start laying eggs!
I heard Karasuno won their match today. Congratulations!
Uh, thanks!
So, I... well, um...
Good luck tomorrow, okay?
Okay, see you later!
Right!
Huh... huh...
You've definitely got a chance there!
Huh!
Yeah!
Yeah, yeah!
After all, home by being with your friends
I think that I'm the most fun things
So, what can I do?
Your brethren Thompson have a more chance
Alright thanks to headset again
We're in London headed for our future
I want to look like a young man
I don't want to stop now
I want to laugh and laugh
I want to laugh
Are you not supposed to try when you have no chance?
Uh, what's that?
Trying when you don't have a chance
Are you talking about Kyoko?
And am I supposed to go for someone else
Just because I do have a chance?
I mean, I get it, I do
If a bunch of hot girls said
Let's play beach volleyball together
Whoops, I'm doing right into you
Obviously I would be down for that
And of course I want hot girls my age
To come cheer for us when we play
But it's different!
Tommy says these are two different things!
We know
We're all well aware that it's just part of who you are, bud
I think we knew it from the very first day you joined
Oh, great
He's on the volleyball team too
Better be sure not to make eye contact
Oh, great
Wow
Ah
Will
Will!
Will?
Will what?
Will you please marry me?
Yeah, no.
It's so good.
I love the proposal at first sight incident.
Perfectly expresses who Tanaka is.
It does.
Yeah.
I'm getting restless thinking about tomorrow.
I'm going to go for a walk.
Is he going to be okay?
I'm just kind of worried that he may be obsessed to the point of turning into a stalker.
I don't think he'd go that far.
He's extremely perceptive about people's feelings, and if Kyoko ever asked him to back off for real, I'm sure he would.
Then he'd disappear.
I know we like to call him an idiot, but he's actually a pretty amazing guy.
He's so simple and so devoted.
I think it's really hard to be that way.
Relief server Tadashi Yamaguchi is making use of his time on the court.
They got us, you guys!
Quiet down, Atsumu!
Huh?
I'm so sorry.
See?
Look what you've done.
One more time!
That's it!
Well done!
Couldn't he see he wouldn't get to it before he hit the wall?
Even if he did, he couldn't return it.
I'm pretty sure the only thing in his mind was the fact that the ball still hadn't actually made contact with the ground.
It's like, I don't know, like he doesn't have the time or brain space to just stop.
Stupid ball!
Clumsy receive, Phil!
The ball is headed back over the net!
We still have a chance.
Kageyama!
Let's go!
Finish it!
I got it!
And the block's into Anna Bills!
Thanks, Kageyama!
Sure.
You played like an ace, Asahi!
Thanks a lot!
Yeah, well, that's his job.
Everyone's totally on their game right now.
Okay, so that can't be legal, right?
Well, neither the player nor the ball went into a Narazaki's court.
It's fine.
Hey, where the hell did you just go?
You missed your boy Tadashi in action!
You dropping a damn deuce?
I needed to rescue Tadashi!
And those stares are brutal.
Man, I hit it right there, number one!
I was trying to aim for number five like Coke said!
It's fine.
And Karasuno manages to get to set point first!
If they miss this chance, the next server will be Atsumumiya.
And I'm pretty sure Karasuno does not want to have to deal with that guy again.
That kid is a menace!
We have a chance.
We definitely have a chance!
Oh, and he is shut down!
The spike was rejected by middle blocker Rintaro Suna!
Nice kill, Rintaro!
That's me.
That was a bit short.
Nah, I totally thought we were gonna make that one work just fine!
If that were me down there, I'd be so pissed off, I'd be spiking the ball right into the net at this point.
He's actually aware of that?
Please, don't let him serve more than once.
Aim your serves at the number five.
He's been out there the entire game and hasn't been making any great plays.
If we're gonna drag them down, it's gotta start with him.
It's coming for me.
I'm used to everyone aiming for me.
Come at me!
Bring it on!
Yeah, there we go!
No way!
Am I just, like, a total loser today?
Come on, guys.
You were their blockers to you.
Frankly, this is not my favorite thing, but...
And Sawa Muna scores from the back row!
Nice one, nice one, guys!
Karasuno has managed to limit the dangerous Atsumomiya to just one serve!
Not too bad, guys.
Nice kill, Daichi!
Thanks!
And now, Karasuno is at set point yet again!
Nice bump!
Oh, that looked like a brand new play.
Why try it with his team facing set point?
Ha ha!
I love it!
Keep it up, young man!
Chance ball!
He's fast.
They're getting their blocks in place!
Even faster than before!
Dammit, man!
It'll take more than that to break my bro!
Yes, ma'am!
Seek quick!
We'll stop it!
Did I hit that one a little hard?
Dammit!
What have I even done today?
Left side!
Tanaka!
What have I accomplished?
Three blockers!
He's overreacting.
Only not really.
Inarizaki's blocking is stubborn.
And that brings with it a sense of desperation.
Add that to the stress of having all the servers go after him,
and a single mistake will be all it takes.
That's enough to make a guy feel like he's doing everything wrong.
Hojitsu Middle School!
Name's Ryunosuke Tanaka!
Sup!
What's with his hair?
I sense a strong will in him.
He's not going to bow down to anybody.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Kurasuno hasn't been performing that well lately.
But in my heart, it's still a powerhouse.
Kurakawa from Hisa Middle School.
Asahi from Sekodai.
Both awesome spikers I saw in tournaments and heard were here.
And from my ear, Nishinoya's here too.
But I don't know.
The reality's not that exciting.
Other teams need the gym today, so we're going to be outside.
Right!
This again?
Why?
Can we go complain to someone?
Hey, it's way better than last year,
and there's plenty of work we can do practicing outside.
What a bunch of damn pushovers.
Thank you very much, guys.
Thanks for the game!
They weren't as tough as I thought they'd be.
I mean, that was barely even a warm-up.
I didn't even break a sweat.
I'll shut them up!
How's that?
Oh, real easy.
I'll just go over when no one's looking and give them a...
Just give them the business!
Let it go!
We should just be grateful they're playing us at all.
And besides, today was our first match with the new team.
We were a mess.
So you're just going to let them say all that about us?
You don't think that's weak?
Just have to win.
It may not be easy, but it's very simple.
Get used to it.
This happens a lot.
Guys are always whispering behind our backs at official matches.
Yeah, they call us...
Karasino's Falling Champions.
Clipped Crows.
Well, their eyes aren't laughing.
All my life, I've seen all my mentors as adults, even if they were only a year older than me.
But I have a different kind of respect for these guys.
It's like somehow I just know...
These guys are strong.
Oh, wow!
What happened to your head, man?
I...
I just thought I should do something to get myself psyched up again.
Let me touch it!
Get out of me!
Lucky!
Yeah, you got that right.
Also, you owe me some pudding.
Not the kind that's sold in three packs.
Huh?
That wasn't me!
They're tied up again!
Can Karasino find a way to pull out of this, Phil?
Did the Orange Team do something especially bad?
That wasn't just a one-time miss.
It's more like the pressure from Inarizaki's blocks is building steadily.
And that miss proved it.
Snap out of it, Tanaka!
That was a good shot!
Yeah, okay!
Damn it!
Push through this, Baldi!
You can do it!
Now's the time to show the world your stuff!
He'll be fine.
Still Tanaka.
He's certainly always been pretty tough during matches.
And of all us second years, with everything that's happened to the team,
no matter what, the one who always stayed...
was Tanaka.
Let's go!
Come on.
This is the part where you're supposed to clam up
and stop being able to look your teammates in the eye.
I got it!
The setter got first contact.
In the front row, that only leaves Tanaka on the left.
Gonna be real hard on the Bald guy, if he can't get this one in.
Well, how do you know he'll end up getting the ball passed to him?
First, it's kind of the standard formula.
And it's also like, the wing spiker on the front row is sort of the last bastion of offense.
And that's how I know.
Shut it!
I didn't call for the ball!
I just...
I lost my focus.
Losing the match doesn't make me pathetic.
Being scared of the match does.
LOOOOO!
Asahi, it's up!
Waterfall ball.
The gridlock continues, Phil.
This could go on all night.
This is quality volleyball.
They didn't pass it to the bald kid, did they?
Nope.
Naruto, get a hold of yourself!
Ryu just keeps getting blocked left and right.
And it's not like you can say Specs made a poor choice,
considering it got them out of the bad groove they were in.
But, well...
Man, that must have really sucked for your boy there, huh?
Tanaka!
Mm-hmm?
That thing before!
When their number 10 came running smack down the middle of the court,
you came into block like, wham!
And it was totally awesome!
A blocker usually ends up by themself when they're blocking in the middle,
but when someone comes to help out, it's like the best!
Seriously!
Wow.
The idiot is saying something decent for once.
Y-you think so?
Oh, totally!
It was like one of Daytec's blocks!
For real!
Still here, but it's all alone.
Yes!
Hinata and Tanaka are killing it!
The natural flatterer and the easily flattered.
It's kind of sad, really.
Nice receive, Daichi!
Now, the rest of you, get the ball over and score some points!
I think I'm just a normal human being.
Normal build, normal abilities.
When I was a kid, I was convinced I was a genius.
No, I guess I still thought that in middle school.
Actually, I still kind of think it now.
But, well, I'll probably never be 180 centimeters tall.
I know I'm a pretty good athlete, but on this volleyball team, at this point in time,
I'm not number one at anything.
But that's not a good reason for me to give up on stuff, and it's not a good excuse.
And honestly, I never even think about that most of the time.
But once every few months, when my confidence takes a nosedive and I'm wallowing in negativity,
I think I'm nothing but average.
And then I think, hey, Mr. Average,
do you really have time to be hanging your head?
Average, do you really have time to be hanging your head?
that guy he's so awesome the relatively unknown contenders take the first set from perennial
powerhouse in nanazaki who knows where the match will go from here wow i was really worried about
us for a while there you know tanaka he usually makes it through okay in the end that's true
was i right am i a freaking genius yeah you sure are sukashima you totally ignored me when i called
it earlier well i figured asahi probably had a better chance of scoring the points so dude how
can you just say it like that it scares me that you somehow have this eternal optimism
don't you ever get depressed yeah i was depressed actually but when just now for several whole
seconds uh huh then i really started thinking about it between super depressed me or aggressive
attacker me which is coolest uh neither obviously aggressive attacker when you in rock bottom
the only way to go is up up and i'm telling you it's not that easy for the rest of us
your man hunk is pretty good unless that was all just a bunch of dumb luck
when i was younger i never liked being called a giant but well
whoa oh wow that was so awesome that block was so high
yeah well you always acted like he was really jealous
and it helped me sincerely think that i do have something special
and that it's something to be proud of
left side
has always been a genuine person so you know
i really think i might be getting my heart broken
away
in
on
See you next time.
Next time, cats versus monkeys.